This is a king of the hill
final battle!
KING OF
THE HILL
FINAL
BATTLE
（皐月(さつき)）塔首(とうしゅ)頂上決戦だ
Matoi! Battle the Four Devas
and emerge victorious!
纏(まとい) 四天王と戦い勝ち抜け
Do so, and I shall tell you the
truth behind your father's death.
そうすれば お前の
父親の死について語ってやろう
Say what?!
（流子(りゅうこ)）何だと
Matoi! This is where
I will face you in battle!
（蟇郡(がまごおり)）纏 これが
お前との戦いの場だ
I am Lady Satsuki's impenetrable shield!
俺は皐月様の絶対の盾
And this is where
I am going to crush you!
貴様ごとき ここで打ち砕く！
I accept!
受けて立つぜ！
Life Fiber Synchronize,
Godrobe Senketsu!
（流子）人衣(じんい)一体 神衣(かむい)鮮血
GODROBE
SENKETSU
FIRST
NATURALS
ELECTION
KING OF
THE HILL
FINAL
BATTLE
What's this? You talk as though
you're going to be the first to fight.
（蛇崩(じゃくずれ)）
おやおや まるであなたが
最初に戦うみたいな口ぶりね
I'll be the first to fight Matoi.
（猿投山(さなげやま)）
纏と戦うのは俺が先だ
Fine by me! I'll take you all on!
いいよ だったら
全員 相手になってやる
You really are a fool.
（犬牟田(いぬむた)）君はバカだね
（流子）何だと！
Say what?!
We said one-on-one, didn't we?
（犬牟田）１対１と言っただろ
We each want to defeat your Godrobe with our own power.
みんな 君の神衣を自分の力で
打ち倒したいんだよ
The battle order
has already been decided.
その順番なら既に決まっている
Haven't you Devas noticed that the
pillars you stand on are of different heights?
（皐月）お前たち四天王の
塔の高さが違うのに気づかないか
The more students you have
defeated, the higher your pillar.
お前たちが倒した生徒の数が
多い順に塔は高くなっている
Gamagoori defeated
the fewest, so he is first.
いちばん低い蟇郡が最初だ
Then Inumuta will fight, followed by Jakuzure, and then Sanageyama.
そのあと犬牟田 蛇崩
猿投山の順に戦え
Damn, I beat too much
of the cannon fodder?
（猿投山）ケッ
雑魚を倒しすぎたか
That efficient fighting style of mine proved effective, I suppose.
（犬牟田）効率的な戦いが
功を奏したかな
Well, well. The one who suggested
this is at the top of the lineup, huh?
なあんだ 結局
言いだしっぺがトップか
It's sweet that you're so considerate of your fellow students, Gama.
ガマちゃん 仲間を大事にするとか
いいとこあるじゃない
All I did was defend
myself when attacked.
（蟇郡）俺は身に降りかかる
火の粉を払っただけだ
Still, I suppose this means that
you three won't get a chance at her!
だが これで お前たちの出番は
なくなったな
What's the holdup?! Get to it already!
どうした 早くしろよ
What are you in such a hurry for?
The battle begins at 1PM!
何を焦っている
塔首頂上決戦は午後１時からだ
（流子）
お！ つーか 時間なんて
どうでもいいだろう
What difference does the time make?
Let's get it over with!
早くやろうぜ
No, we will abide by the schedule.
いや 時間は守る
That is what discipline is about!
それが風紀だ それが規律だ！
That is what the rules are about!
EPISODE 9
A ONCE IN A
LIFETIME CHANCE
This is a world tailored to someone's whims and fancies
dareka ga katteni kimeta readymade na
I'll break free of its shackles
kyou wo nugisutete
RYUUKO
MATOI
And sprint toward my goal
hadashi de hashitte iku
Even if I lose my way
machigattatte
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
Or trip and fall
korondatte
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
Those wounds will still create
surimuita itami mo
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
An original future for me
original na ashita ni naru
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
I hold my destiny in my own hands
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
And it shines ever so brightly
chikai ga hikari ni natte
So until the day I reach you
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
I don't have the time to sit around crying
naiteru hima nante nai kara
My burning passion pours out from within me
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
And shines like a star in the night sky
yozora de kagayaki dasu
I think I now understand
umarete kita imi ga
Why I was born
wakatta ki ga shita
I'll make all of my dreams come true
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
With my own hands
kanaeru
The Honnouji Academy King of the Hill
Final Battle will be held starting at 1PM today.
（拡声器:女性）
本日 午後１時より—
本能字(ほんのうじ)学園
塔首頂上決戦が行われます
本能字学園 生徒会四天王と—
It will be a bloody clash between the
Honnouji Academy Student Council Four Devas
２年甲組 纏流子が
血で血を洗う大激突
and Matoi Ryuuko of Class 2-A.
Special live coverage will be
brought to you by Honnouji Television!
本能字テレビジョンで
緊急生放送
Grandmas, grandpas, fathers, mothers,
おじいちゃん おばあちゃん
お父さん お母さん
and good little boys and girls,
let's sit back and enjoy the show!
よい子のみんなも
みんなで見よう
What? Ryuuko's gonna fight them?!
（薔薇蔵(ばらぞう)）
何！ 流子ちゃんが？
こうしちゃいられねえ
We can't just sit here!
Matarou, go steal us a
TV set from somewhere!
又郎(またろう) どっかから
テレビかっぱらってこい
（又郎）
へい こんなこともあろうかと
もうとっくに用意してらぁ！
No prob! I already got us one
for just such an occasion!
Attaboy, Matarou!
（薔薇蔵）でかした 又郎
（好代(すくよ)）でも映んないよ
It's not showing anything.
Huh?
（又郎）あれー？
（薔薇蔵）え… え？ たたくのね
（又郎）あれー
You try hitting it?
...Better open it up...
（又郎）蓋 開けぇの
（薔薇蔵）開けて はい
Got it.
...Then poke around inside...
（又郎）突っ込みぃの
（薔薇蔵）ええ 突っ込んでね はい
...Poke around...
（薔薇蔵）入るのね
はいはいはいはい
What's in here?
（又郎）うう…
な な… ないね
Nothing, looks like.
（薔薇蔵）入るのね
はいはいはいはい
There aren't any parts inside!
（薔薇蔵）
中身がないんじゃないか！
仕方ねえ電器屋に行くぞ
Fine! Let's go to the electronics store!
（好代）アイアイサー
Aye-aye, sir!
I'm coming too!
（又郎）あっ 俺も うう…
No(ノー) more(モア) テレビドロボー
No more TV stealing for me!
（流子）あぐっ
Here, Ryuuko! Have some tea!
First
Naturals
Election
First
Naturals
Election
（マコ）はい 流子ちゃん お茶
（流子）おう
うっうっ ぷはー
Yeah!
Eating Mom's boxed lunches
gives you one million horsepower!
（マコ）かあちゃんのお弁当
食べれば百万馬力だよ
絶対勝つよ
You'll win for sure!
What a pickle this is, Matoi.
（美木杉(みきすぎ)）いやあ
大変なことになったね 纏君
（マコ）あっ 美木杉先生
Mr. Mikisugi!
Did you come to
cheer Ryuuko on, too?
先生も流子ちゃんの応援に
来てくれたんですか？
Yes, that's right.
そうそう 僕も一応
纏君の担任だからね
After all, I'm her homeroom
teacher, more or less.
（流子）あっ てめえ
マコに何しやがった
You bastard!
What did you do to Mako?!
（美木杉）フッ 不動のツボ
I triggered a pressure point.
She'll just be out for a
little bit, so don't worry.
ちょっと意識を
飛ばしてるだけだから心配するな
So what the hell do you want?
で 何の用だよ
Drop out of the fight
against the Four Devas.
（美木杉）
四天王戦は棄権したまえ
あっ 何だと
Say what?!
They're on an entirely different level
from the club presidents you've faced.
四天王はほかの部長とは
レベルが違う
それが４人連続なんて無理をすると
君と鮮血に何が起こるかわからない
If you're crazy enough to
face four of them in a row,
I don't know what will happen
to you and Senketsu.
If you don't know,
spare me the lecture.
（流子）わからないんだったら
余計な口を出すな
...Ryuuko...
（美木杉）流子君…
Or are you finally
going to tell me everything?
（流子）それとも あんたが
全部 話してくれんのか
Like why my father was killed.
父さんがなぜ殺されたのか
I... can't do that.
（美木杉）それは… 無理だ
Then sit down, shut up, and watch.
（流子）
だったら黙って見てな
Senketsu and I will
beat Kiryuuin Satsuki.
あたしと鮮血が鬼龍院(きりゅういん)皐月を倒す
And then I'll wring the truth out of her.
そして あいつの口から聞きだす
With my own two hands.
あたしの手でね
Hurry up and bring Mako back.
早くマコの意識を戻してくれ
こいつと話してるほうが
よっぽど元気になるんだ
Talking to her makes me feel a
whole lot better than talking to you.
I'll be cheering for her all the way!
私 断然 応援するんです
Because she's my friend!
だって友達だもん
（美木杉）うんうん
まあ 無理しないでね
Yes, of course! Don't push
yourself too hard, okay?
君のせいで僕まで生徒会に
にらまれるのは嫌だからね
I'd rather not end up on the
Student Council's bad side because of you.
Is something the matter?
（マコ）ん？ どうかしたの
（流子）
ん？ お… おいしいよ
マコのお母さんのお弁当
Nope! Your mom's
lunches are delicious!
Seriously, they're great.
ホントにおいしい
Begin!
始めろ
King Of
The Hill
Round 1
Matoi Ryuuko
vs.
Gamagoori
Ira
King Of
The Hill
Round 1
Matoi Ryuuko
vs.
Gamagoori
Ira
The Hill
Matoi Ryuuko
vs.
Gamagoori
Ira
Begin
Fighting
His Ultima Uniform
has a double transformation.
（流子）ヤツの極(ごく)制服は
二段変身する 手ごわいぞ
He's a tough customer.
You listening, Senketsu?
（流子）おい 鮮血
（鮮血）あっ ああ
Oh. Yes.
どうした？
What's wrong?
Nothing, really.
（鮮血）いや ちょっと
Were you thinking about something?
（流子）何か考え事か？
Possibly.
（鮮血）まあな
He's a formidable enemy.
Keep your mind on the fight.
強敵だ 戦いに集中してくれ
I know. I will.
（鮮血）ああ わかってる
Let's do it!
いくぞ！
Consider that your
final transformation, Matoi!
それが最後の変身と思え 纏！
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
Shackle Regalia!
THREE
STAR
ULTIMA
UNIFORM
SHACKLE REGALIA
Hey.
（蟇郡）おい
（流子）あ？
What?
Do you want to fight or not?!
（蟇郡）やる気あるのか
（流子）当然
Of course!
（蟇郡）だったら
なぜ攻撃してこない
Then why aren't you attacking me?!
I'll throw what your buddy said this morning back in your face.
さっき お前の仲間に
言われた言葉を返すよ
You really are a fool, aren't ya?
（流子）お前 バカだろ
（蟇郡）何？
What did you say?
I know that your Ultima Uniform absorbs the power of
any attacks against you and turns it back on the attacker!
（流子）お前の極制服が自分への
攻撃パワーをため込んで—
相手に返すことは
わかってるんだ
Why would I attack you?
うかつに手を
出すわけないだろうが
I see. So you really are a fool.
（蟇郡）なるほど
やはり貴様はバカだな
何だと？
Come again?
Do you think that I wouldn't
anticipate something so obvious?
（蟇郡）その程度のことを
考えない俺だと思うか
What the...
何？
Even if no one disciplines me,
I discipline myself!
（蟇郡）誰も俺を攻めなくても
俺が俺を攻める
I use my own techniques
to punish myself!
自分の技で自分を攻める
I punish and punish and punish, bringing myself to a climax!
攻めて攻めて 攻め抜いて
自分で頂点に達する
これぞ秘技…
This is my Secret Technique:
Self-Flagellation!
SECRET
TECHNIQUE
SELF
FLAGELLATION
（流子）そんなのありかよ
No way!
Now, let me show you!
（蟇郡）見せてやろう
THREE
STAR
Three-Star Ultima Uniform:
Scourge Regalia!
ULTIMA UNIFORM
SCOURGE REGALIA
（流子）どわっ
（猿投山）フゥ
What are you waiting for?
（蟇郡）どうした
If you fall out of the battle area, you lose right then and there!
このバトルエリアから落ちたら
その時点で お前の負けだ
Nobody said that was a rule!
そんなルール聞いてねえ
That's why I'm telling you now!
Are we clear, Matoi?
（蟇郡）だから今 言ったのだ
理解したな 纏
Crystal clear!
おかげさまで しっかりとね
Thank you ever so much!
You acknowledge that a contest
of endurance against me is futile?
（蟇郡）我慢比べは
無駄なことがわかったろ
さあ 次はどうする
All right, what's your next move?
In that case, it's business as usual!
だったら…
正攻法でいくだけだ！
Finishing Move: Thread Stripper!
必殺…
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
あれ？
Huh?
His uniform has no
Life Fibers on its surface.
（鮮血）ヤツの表面には
生命戦維がない
ない以上 吸収できない
There is nothing for me to absorb!
えっ そんな
No way!
（蟇郡）驚いたか
この縛の装の表面は—
Surprised? My Shackle Regalia's
surface is cloth armor,
reinforced by means of special powers.
特殊能力で強化加工されている
布の鎧(よろい)だ
To absorb its Life Fibers,
you will have to pierce this cloth armor
生命戦維を吸収したければ
この布の鎧を切り裂き—
and thrust your blade
into the uniform proper!
本体まで その刃(やいば)を
突き立てることだ
Then I'll just have to cut
all the way to the inside!
（流子）だったら…
一気に中まで斬ればいい
（蟇郡）いいのか？
Is that wise?
If you attack me,
I become that much stronger!
お前が攻撃すれば
それだけ俺の力になる
（蟇郡）死縛(しばき)の装
（流子）うわっ
Scourge Regalia!
Ryuuko!
流子ちゃん！
Stardust Electronics
Look out!
（薔薇蔵）危ない！
This is bad!
（又郎）ヤバいよ さすが四天王
流子の姉御が押されてる
That's the Four Devas for you! He has Ryuuko on the ropes!
Don't you worry.
She ate the lunch I made for her.
大丈夫よ
流子ちゃんは私の作ったお弁当を
食べてるんだもん
So she can't possibly lose!
負けるわけがない
Impressive. That Godrobe is far more
potent than any other Ultima Uniform.
（蟇郡）さすが神衣だ
与えてくれる力は
ほかの極制服と桁違いだな
これだけ長時間
死縛の装で戦えるとは—
It gives me the power I need to wield
...my Scourge Regalia ever longer—
your very own power, Matoi!
お前自身の力を恨め 纏
Oh, dear. What's wrong
with the transfer student?
あらあら
どうしちゃったのかな 転校生
意外と手応えないじゃない
She's more of a pushover
than I was expecting.
The Disciplinary Bureau Chairman's
forehead is more wrinkled than usual.
（犬牟田）
風紀部委員長 いつも以上に
眉間に しわが入ってるね
Because to him, this is a fight
in the presence of his empress.
（猿投山）ヤツにとっては
天覧試合だからな
No wonder he's giving it his all.
気合いも入ろう
Matoi.
纏 蟇郡という男の覚悟
半端ではないぞ
The resolve of this man,
Gamagoori, is nothing to sneeze at.
FIVE
YEARS
AGO
Rinne-Dou
Junior High
63Rd
Graduation
Ceremony
To think that such an earnest former council president
would skip his own graduation ceremony...
（皐月）謹厳実直
元生徒会長の貴様が
卒業式をサボるとはな
If you intend to rule
this school with force,
（蟇郡）お前が力でこの学校を
支配しようとするのなら—
then I will stop you at all costs!
俺はなんとしても止める
That is the final task I must
carry out at this school!
それが俺がこの学校で
しなければならない—
最後の仕事だ うおお！
（皐月）ほう
Steel armor over your entire body, eh?
全身に鉄の鎧か
Courtesy of my relatives,
who run an ironworks.
（蟇郡）親戚が鉄工所を
やっているので作ってもらった
貴様の攻撃は効かん
Your attacks won't work on me!
（皐月）だが それでは
私に勝てない
Be that as it may,
you cannot defeat me.
I never thought that I could.
（蟇郡）勝てるとは思わん
俺の力では
お前を倒すことはできん
My own strength
is not nearly enough.
If you know that,
then why do you oppose me?
（皐月）
それがわかっていながら
なぜあらがう
勝てないが負けもしない
I can't defeat you,
but I won't lose to you either!
What did you say?
何だと
You can't make me
kneel before you.
お前に俺を
ひざまずかせることはできない
お前が力でこの学校を
屈服させるつもりなら—
If you intend to use force
to conquer this school,
I'll take all of it on myself!
俺はそれを全て受けてみせる
力では決して屈しない
存在があるということを—
I'll show you that there are those who will never yield to force.
お前に見せてやる
それが俺の覚悟だ
That is my resolve!
Easily said, somewhat
more difficult to do.
言うは易(やす)く行うは難し
口だけなら容赦せぬぞ
If your words are hollow,
expect no mercy!
（蟇郡）ハァ ハァ…
I won't kneel before you... Never!
ひざまずかん 絶対に
I'll never kneel before you!
絶対にひざまずかん
Did... Did I lose?
俺は… 負けたのか…
Gamagoori. I have seen the
full measure of your resolve.
（皐月）蟇郡 貴様の覚悟
確かに見届けた
Come with me, and become my shield.
私と共に来てくれ
そして私の盾となってくれ
何を考えている？ あなたは…
What are you planning?
People are pigs in human clothing.
（皐月）人間は服を着た豚だ
I will fight against everything
this world stands for
私はこの世界の全てと戦い
全てをつくり直す
and completely remake it.
As the first stage of my plan, I will
create a new high school in two years' time.
その一歩として２年後
新しい高校をつくる
私の軍団となる高校だ
A high school that will be my army.
Join me there, and you will
be able to attain new strength.
そこに来れば貴様は新しい力を
手に入れることができる
わかった ２年待とう
Very well. I will wait two years.
I told you: I am Lady
Satsuki's ultimate shield!
（蟇郡）言ったはずだ
俺は皐月様の最強の盾だ
ここで お前を打ち砕く
I will crush you here and now!
Like hell you will!
冗談じゃない お前なんかに
負けるわけにはいかねえんだよ
I'm not about to lose to you!
What are you even fighting for?
（蟇郡）
貴様の戦いは何のためだ
父親を殺された怒りか？
Vengeance for your father's murder?
You're petty! Petty! Petty!
小さいぞ 小さい小さい
貴様のように私怨で挑んでも—
An attack driven by a
mere personal vendetta
鬼龍院皐月という存在は
小揺るぎもせぬわ
wouldn't even scratch a
great being like Kiryuuin Satsuki!
何！
What?!
（蟇郡）皐月様だけではない
この俺も倒すことはできん
And not just her!
You'll never be able to defeat me either!
Oh, gosh!
なんとー
Are you all right, Ryuuko?
（鮮血）大丈夫か 流子
Yeah. I'm in rough shape, though.
ああ かなり厳しいけどな
But I can't drop out. Not now.
だけど ここで
引くわけにはいかねえ
（蟇郡）フン！
バカなうえに諦めも悪いか
So not only are you a fool,
but you're also a bad loser.
What's bad around here is your luck.
悪いのは お前の運だよ
あたしと戦うハメになった
お前のな！
Your bad luck for getting
stuck with fighting me!
Don't do that!
（又郎）げー！ ダメだよ
そんなやみくもに攻撃しちゃ
You can't just wail on him
without a plan like that!
He'll hit you with another counterattack!
（薔薇蔵）
また ぶっといの食らうぞ
Is it out of desperation?
やけくそかしら…
That's no good.
（美木杉）ダメだ
とうとう判断力が停止したかな
Has she finally lost all capacity
for rational thought?
Struggle all you want!
You don't have a chance of winning!
（蟇郡）いくらあがこうと
貴様に勝機はない
Learn your place as a student
and quietly accept my discipline!
学生の本分を知って
おとなしく 俺の粛清を受けろ
Scourge Regalia!
死縛の装
As if! If I lose to the likes of you,
冗談じゃない
てめえなんかに負けてちゃ—
I'll never learn who killed my dad, no matter how long I try!
いつまでたったも父さんの敵(かたき)に
たどりつかねえんだよ
いいよー 流子ちゃん
Go get him, Ryuuko!
It still hasn't gotten through
that thick skull of yours?
（蟇郡）
ここまで言ってもわからんか
I am Disciplinary Bureau
Chairman Gamagoori Ira!
風紀部委員長 蟇郡苛(いら)
己を縛り ムチ打ち
きつく戒めることで—
By shackling and whipping
myself mercilessly,
生徒の規範とならんとした
I tried to set an example
for the students.
"See my behavior,
and correct your own!"
俺の振り見て我が振り直せ
自らの意思で自らの襟を正す
"Mend your ways of your own accord!"
本能字学園の生徒たちの
自主性に規律を託す
I wish to entrust Honnouji Academy's order to the independence of its students,
その思いの結実が縛(しばり)の装である
and the Shackle Regalia is the
very embodiment of that desire!
To those who still refuse to learn,
そして それでも
わからぬ者には—
I hold back my tears and give them a taste of the cleansing whip!
涙をのんで粛清のムチを
振るった
That is the Scourge Regalia!
これが死縛の装である
If you refuse the whip of love,
then you leave me no other choice!
その愛のムチを
ここまで拒否するならば…
仕方がない
Let me show you the true terror
of the Shackle Regalia!
死縛の装の本当の恐ろしさ
見せてやろう
Matoi Ryuuko,
your independence is revoked!
纏流子 貴様の自主性は
見限った
I'm going to mold you
into a proper student!
とことん型にはめてやる！
Where do you get off, anyway,
だいたい何だ貴様は
セーラー服を改造して
そんな破廉恥な格好にして
modifying your sailor uniform
into that slutty outfit?!
まさに不良 まさに逸脱
How utterly depraved!
How utterly deviant!
だったら皐月はどうなんだよ
What about your precious
Lady Satsuki, then?!
She is an exception!
皐月様は例外だ
Her form is forged from her
iron will and well-trained body.
（蟇郡）皐月様は
鍛えられた肉体と—
鋼鉄の意思で
あの姿になられている
（流子）てめえ勝手なこと
言ってんじゃねえ
Don't give me that
self-serving garbage!
Crap! I'm wrapped up!
しまった
絞められた
（蟇郡）フハハハハッ
図星をつかれて動揺したか
Oh? Did I manage to strike a nerve?
さあ 纏流子
今 俺が型にはめてやる
All right, Matoi Ryuuko,
it's time to mold you into shape!
This mold is of the ideal,
proper high school girl.
この型は期待される
正しき女子高生像
気持ちを正すには まず形から
"A proper spirit starts with a proper shape."
...Have a taste of this mold...
この型を食らって—
and reflect on your wicked ways!
反省するがいい あがけあがけ
Struggle! Struggle!
うわー あれじゃ まるで
人間たい焼きだよ
She's like a toasted human sandwich!
I won't give up!
俺は諦めない
諦めず粘り強く お前を正す
I won't rest until I've
straightened you out!
I will mold you!
Mold you into a proper student!
型にはめて はめつくす
（鮮血）勝ちたいか 流子
Do you want to win, Ryuuko?
こんなときに何 当たり前のこと
聞いてくる
You're asking me such
an obvious question now?!
（鮮血）だったら私に考えがある
If you do, I have an idea.
さっき考えてたことか？
That thing you were
thinking about earlier?
（鮮血）ああ 任せてくれるか？
Yes. Will you let me handle this?
Got it!
わかった
Ah, she used the power released when disengaging her transformation to break free of the shackles.
変身解除したときの力で
リングから抜けたか
でもそれじゃ勝ち目はない
But she doesn't have a
hope of winning like that.
Oh, so my words
finally got through to you?
（蟇郡）ほほう
俺の言葉が通じたか
少しはまともな姿に
戻ったようだな
I see that you have returned
to a more proper appearance!
（流子）誰が お前なんかに
この変態野郎！
Who would listen
to you, you big pervert?
In that case, taste the
ultimate whip of love!
（蟇郡）ならば
究極の愛のムチを味わえ
（マコ）キャー
（蟇蒲）
フッ “窮鳥 懐に入らずんば”の
故事にでも習う気か？
So, you're applying the idea that "even the
hunter spares the bird that flies to his bosom"?
I must warn you, however,
that I'm not that sentimental!
だが俺はそんなに甘くない
I'll choke the life
from you here and now!
このまま絞めおとしてやろう
Having trouble breathing?
（蟇郡）苦しいか
But without your Sword Scissor, you have no way to fight back!
だが片太刀バサミのない
お前に反撃する手段はない
Uh-oh. Is it all over?
あらら 決まっちゃった？
A shame. I was hoping to
gather more Godrobe data.
（犬牟田）神衣のデータが
欲しかったんだけどな
No! What's this I'm sensing?
（猿投山）いや これは
Gamagoori, that was foolish.
（皐月）蟇郡 おろかな
Life Fiber Synchronize!
What?!
（蟇郡）何？
Senketsu Blade Flash!
SENKETSU
BLADE FLASH
She turned her Godrobe into a blade?
神衣を刃にしただと
You don't have enough energy to
transform into your Scourge Regalia!
（流子）死縛の装にするには
エネルギーが足りねえだろ
もう遅い
Too late!
Your Life Fibers are
totally exposed now!
てめえの生命戦維 丸見えだ
Finishing Move: Thread Stripper!
必殺 戦維喪失
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
I-Impossible!
（蟇郡）バ… バカな
Become obsessed with resolve,
and even that will turn to arrogance.
覚悟も溺れれば おごりとなる
無念だな
A shame.
King Of
The Hill
Round 1
Victor
Matoi
Ryuuko
You did it, Ryuuko!
やったよ流子ちゃん
Just like you planned, Senketsu!
狙いどおりだったな 鮮血
If an Ultima Uniform can transform,
（鮮血）極制服が変形するなら
私にだってやれないはずはない
it would be unthinkable to
suggest I could not do the same.
That positive outlook of yours is what I love about you, Senketsu!
（流子）そういう
前向きな考え方 好きだぞ
It learned to alter its configuration based on battlefield conditions.
（美木杉）戦局による
形状変化まで会得するとは—
I'm impressed, Ryuuko.
さすがだよ 流子君
けど 素直には喜べないなぁ
Still, I guess I can't
simply be happy about it.
Disgraceful!
ぶざまなり…
That was disgraceful, Gamagoori Ira!
ぶざまなり 蟇郡苛
...Lady... Satsuki...
皐月… 様
Wipe away your own tears.
自分の涙は自分で拭え
It's too early to kneel in defeat.
まだ ひざまずくには早い
That's one down, Kiryuuin!
（流子）とりあえず
１人倒したぜ 鬼龍院
（犬牟田）ということは
（流子）あっ？
...I suppose that means...
（犬牟田）次の相手は
俺ということになるね 纏君
...that I will be your ...
next opponent, Matoi.
（流子）フン
You are free to rest, Matoi!
（皐月）休息してもいいぞ 纏
Get real!
冗談じゃねえ
とっとと雑魚は片づけて—
I gotta waste your chumps
and then come after you!
てめえの相手しねえと
いけねえからなぁ
...Ryuuko...
流子ちゃん
Okay, let's get to it.
（流子）さあ 始めようぜ
So impatient.
（犬牟田）せっかちだねえ
Still, I hate to waste time
just as much as you do.
ま 時間のロスは俺も嫌いなんだ
Before the bell rings
chime ga naru mae ni
I sneak out of school
kugurinuketa
Avoiding the adults' vacant stares
otonatachi no haiiro no me
The pointless conversations
tawai no nai kaiwa
Keep going on and on
togirenu mama
As I walk down the slope
sakamichi wo kudatteku
I have nothing to do
nani wo suru demo naku
And nowhere to go
yuku ate sae mo naku
Right now, all I do
tada atashi ima wa ne
Is ignore any and all warnings
donna chuukoku mo mimi wo surinukeru
Because I still want to be free
mada mada suki ni sasete
I'm sorry, but it's not like me
gomen ne e ni kaita you na
To be an exemplary student
yuutosei wa rashiku nai wa
So I undo two of my shirt buttons
shirt no button wo futatsu hazushite
And take the back alley
rojiura no nukemichi
A path of mysterious sweet temptation
amai yuuwaku wa michi
Some things I've kept hidden from everyone
dare ni mo mada hanashite nai
But tonight, I will reveal my secrets to you
atashi no himitsu wo kon'ya oshiete ageru
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
To be skilled at searching out
information is to be skilled at love.
（鮮血）
検索上手は恋上手
Inputting opponent data! To be skilled at analysis is to be skilled at love!
相手のデータをインプット
DATA
分析上手は恋上手
ANALYSIS
気持ちの先読み おこたりなし
Meticulously observe where
one's feelings are headed!
METICULOUSLY
男と女 勝つのはどっち
MAN VERSUS WOMAN
It's man versus woman:
who will win?!
次回 キルラキル
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"I Want to Know More about You"!
「あなたを･もっと･知りたくて」
EPISODE 10
I WANT TO KNOW MORE ABOUT YOU